Anywhere is possible.
Jumper is a action, adventure, science fiction film directed by Doug Liman.
David Rice is a man who knows no boundaries, a Jumper, born with the
uncanny ability to teleport instantly to anywhere on Earth.
When he discovers others like himself, David is thrust into a dangerous and bloodthirsty war while being
hunted by a sinister and determined group of zealots who have sworn to destroy all Jumpers.
Now, David’s extraordinary gift may be his only hope for survival!
David Rice, played by Hayden Christensen.
Griffin, played by Jamie Bell.
Roland, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Millie Harris, played by Rachel Bilson.
William Rice, played by Michael Rooker.
Mary Rice, played by Diane Lane.
Jumper is a 2008 American science fiction action film
directed by Doug Liman and written by David S.
Goyer, Jim Uhls and Simon Kinberg.
Loosely based on  the 1992 novel by Steven Gould, the film stars Hayden Christensen as a young man
capable of teleporting, as he is pursued by a secret society intent on killing him.
Jamie Bell, Rachel Bilson, Max Thieriot, AnnaSophia Robb,
Diane Lane, Michael Rooker, and Samuel L.
Jackson also star.
The script went through a rewrite prior to filming, and the roles for
the main characters were changed during production.
Filmed in 20 cities and 14 countries from 2007 to 2008 and released on February 14, 2008, the film grossed $225 million worldwide and received
generally negative reviews from critics, mostly because of the many changes to Gould's novel, rushed plot, and anticlimactic ending.
The film explores themes of adolescence, based on novel
or book, teleportation, chase, fight.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.